Becker, Frank J.; Papers apap224
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Correspondence, 1953-1964; 2; 2.4 cubic ft.
  - Veterans, F, 1955-1956 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 4)
  - Veterans, F, 1956-1958 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - Veterans, F, 1959 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 6)
  - Veterans, F, 1960 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 7)
  - Veterans, F, 1961 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 8)
  - Veterans, F, 1963-1964 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 9)
  - Veterans, Fertsch, Eugene H., 1953 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 10)
  - Veterans, Fraser, William, 1953 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 11)
  - Veterans, G, 1954 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 12)
  - Veterans, G, 1955-1956 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Veterans, G, 1957-1958 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 14)
  - Veterans, G, 1959-1960 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Veterans, G, 1960-1962 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 16)
  - Veterans, G, 1963-1964 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 17)
  - Veterans, Geyer, John, 1953 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 18)
  - Veterans, H, 1953 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 19)
  - Veterans, H, 1956 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 20)
  - Veterans, H, 1957-1958 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 21)
  - Veterans, H, 1959-1960 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 22)
  - Veterans, H, 1961-1962 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 23)
  - Veterans, H, 1963-1964 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 24)
  - Veterans, Heinsohn, George, 1954 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 25)
  - Veterans, Hendrickson, Lawrence, 1954 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 26)
  - Veterans, Henne, Grant, 1954 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 27)
  - Veterans, I, 1962 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 28)
  - Veterans, I, 1963 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 29)
  - Veterans, J, 1954-1956 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 30)
  - Veterans, J, 1957-1958 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 31)
  - Veterans, J, 1960 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 32)
  - Veterans, J, 1960-1961 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 33)
  - Veterans, J, 1963 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 34)
  - Veterans, Jacobs, F.H., 1953 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 35)
  - Veterans, Johnson, William V., 1953 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 36)
  - Veterans, K, 1955-1956 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 37)
  - Veterans, K, 1957-1958 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 38)
  - Veterans, K, 1959-1960 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 39)
  - Veterans, K, 1960-1962 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 40)
  - Veterans,Kelly, James, J., 1954 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 41)
  - Veterans, Kessler, Merlyn, 1952-1953 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 42)
  - Veterans, Kostyrka, Edward, 1953 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 43)
  - Veterans, L, 1953-1956 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 44)
  - Veterans, L, 1955-1956 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 45)
  - Veterans, L, 1957 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 46)
  - Veterans, L, 1959-1960 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 47)
  - Veterans, L, 1961-1963 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 48)
  - Veterans, L, 1961-1963 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 49)
  - Veterans, Law, Alma, 1963 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 50)
  - Veterans, Lee, Harry, J., 1953 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 51)
  - Veterans, Lockwood, Harold, W., 1953 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 52)
  - Veterans, M, 1955-1956 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 53)
  - Veterans, M, 1957-1958 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 54)
  - Veterans, M, 1959-1960 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 55)
  - Veterans, M, 1961-1962 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 56)
  - Veterans, M, 1963-1964 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 57)
  - Veterans, Madden, Thomas, 1953 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 58)
  - Veterans, Mahady, Roy, 1953 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 1)
  - Veterans, Charles, J., 1953-1954; 1956; 1958 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 2)
  - Veterans, Malone, John, Wm., 1953-1954 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 3)
  - Veterans, Marshall, John, F., 1953 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 4)
  - Veterans, Maus, Albert, 1953 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - Veterans, Mc, 1954 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 6)
  - Veterans, Mc, 1955-1956 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 7)
  - Veterans, Mc, 1957-1958 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 8)
  - Veterans, Mc, 1960 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 9)
  - Veterans, Mc, 1961 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 10)
  - Veterans, Mc, 1964 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 11)
  - Veterans, Mierjeski, Raymond, 1953 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 12)
  - Veterans, Miscellaneous, 1953 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Veterans, Molusky, Catherine, 1953-1954 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 14)
  - Veterans, Morrison, Hugh R., 1953 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Veterans, Mott, James, L., 1953 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 16)
  - Veterans, N, 1956 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 17)
  - Veterans, N, 1957-1958 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 18)
  - Veterans, N, 1959 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 19)
  - Veterans, N, 1961-1962 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 20)
  - Veterans, N, 1963 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 21)
  - Veterans, O, 1954 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 22)
  - Veterans, O, 1955-1956 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 23)
  - Veterans, O, 1959-1960 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 24)
  - Veterans, O, 1963 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 25)
  - Veterans, O'Brien, John, J., 1958-1959 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 26)
  - Veterans, Offermann, Charles, 1953 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 27)
  - Veterans, Ornauer, Richard, 1954 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 28)
  - Veterans, Ostrov, Alfred, 1953 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 29)
  - Veterans, P, 1955-1956 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 30)
  - Veterans, P, 1957 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 31)
  - Veterans, P, 1958-1960 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 32)
  - Veterans, P, 1961-1962 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 33)
  - Veterans, P, 1963-1964 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 34)
  - Veterans, Q, 1955-1956 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 35)
  - Veterans, R, 1954 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 36)
  - Veterans, R, 1955-1956 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 37)
  - Veterans, R, 1957-1958 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 38)
  - Veterans, R, 1959-1960 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 39)
  - Veterans, R, 1961-1962 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 40)
  - Veterans, R, 1962-1963 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 41)
  - Veterans, Raider, Alvin, 1953 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 42)
  - Veterans, Rogers, Ralph E., 1954-1955 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 43)
  - Veterans, S, 1955-1956 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 44)
  - Veterans, S, 1957-1958 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 45)
  - Veterans, S, 1958-1959 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 46)
  - Veterans, S, 1959-1960 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 47)
  - Veterans, S, 1961 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 48)
  - Veterans, S, 1963-1964 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 49)
  - Veterans, Schiller, Barry, 1953 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 50)
  - Veterans, Schnurr, Francis, 1953 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 51)
  - Veterans, Schuberth, Suzanne, L., 1953-1954 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 52)
  - Veterans, Scuderi, James, 1954 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 53)
  - Veterans, Shannon, Joseph, P., 1954 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 54)
  - Veterans, Shields, Thomas, 1954 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 55)
  - Veterans, Slack, Milton, 1953 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 56)
  - Veterans, Smith, Albert, 1954 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 57)
  - Veterans, Smith, Alfred Conklin, 1953 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 58)
  - Veterans, Smith, Kenneth, P., 1952-1953 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 59)
  - Veterans, Southard, Joseph, 1954 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 60)
  - Veterans, Stern, George, 1953 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 61)
  - Veterans, Stulz, Joseph, 1953-1954 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 62)
  - Veterans, T, 1955-1956 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 63)
  - Veterans, T, 1956-1958 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 64)
  - Veterans, T, 1960 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 65)
  - Veterans, T, 1960-1961 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 66)
  - Veterans, T, 1961-1962 (Box 17 (2-Correspondence), Folder 67)
  - Veterans, T, 1963-1964 (Box 18 (2-Correspondence), Folder 1)
  - Veterans, T, 1954 (Box 18 (2-Correspondence), Folder 2)
  - Veterans, V, 1955 (Box 18 (2-Correspondence), Folder 3)
  - Veterans, V, 1958 (Box 18 (2-Correspondence), Folder 4)
  - Veterans, V, 1963 (Box 18 (2-Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - Veterans, W, 1955-1956 (Box 18 (2-Correspondence), Folder 6)
  - Veterans, W, 1956-1958 (Box 18 (2-Correspondence), Folder 7)
  - Veterans, W, 1959-1960 (Box 18 (2-Correspondence), Folder 8)
  - Veterans, W, 1961-1962 (Box 18 (2-Correspondence), Folder 9)
  - Veterans, W, 1962-1964 (Box 18 (2-Correspondence), Folder 10)
  - Veterans, Walsh, Richard, 1953 (Box 18 (2-Correspondence), Folder 11)
  - Veterans, Ward, Elwood R., 1957 (Box 18 (2-Correspondence), Folder 12)
  - Veterans, Welsh, Robert J., 1953 (Box 18 (2-Correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Veterans, Witten, Elsie, 1953 (Box 18 (2-Correspondence), Folder 14)
  - Veterans, Wordraska, Joseph P., 1957-1958 (Box 18 (2-Correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Veterans, Z, 1958 (Box 18 (2-Correspondence), Folder 16)
  - Veterans, Z, 1960 (Box 18 (2-Correspondence), Folder 17)
- Legislative Files, 1953-1964; Undated; 3; 2.4 cubic ft.
  Arranged chronologically by legislation introduction date.
  This series contains legislation introduced by Frank Becker with related correspondence, copies of the bills, reports, and printed matter. For the majority of legislative bills through 1962, Becker's Congressional office created two files a main file and one designated for general correspondence. News releases may be filed in either location. All the information contained in the folder titles (the legislation's date of introduction, bill number and title) appeared on the original files created by Becker's office. The series is arranged by the introduction number of the bills; however related materials in the folders may contain additional dates. Please note there is a noticeable gap with no legislative files donated for the years between 1957 and 1961.
  - Introduced March 5, 1953, H.R. 3685, Authorizing VA Administrator to Furnish Space in Veteran Facilities, State Vet Agencies, 1953-1954 (Box 1 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 1-2)
  - Introduced March 5, 1953, H.R. 3685, Material for Presenting to Committee on Veteran Affairs (Box 1 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 3)
  - Introduced April 1, 1953, H.R. 4391, Exempt from Tax Cigarettes Sold to Veterans' Organizations for Distr. As Gifts, to Hospitalized Veterans, 1953-1954; Undated (Box 1 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 4)
  - Introduced April 1, 1953, H.R. 4391, Cigarette Bill, General Correspondence, 1954 (Box 1 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 5)
  - Introduced April 21, 1953, H.R. 4714, To Apply War Claims Act to Allied Prisoners of War, 1953-1954; Undated (Box 1 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 6)
  - Introduced May 21, 1953, H.R. 5335, Provide for the Development and Beneficial Public Use of the Power of the Niagara Falls, Undated (Box 1 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 7-8)
  - Introduced June 2, 1953, H.R. 5511, For the Relief of Clara Gabriel, 1953-1954 (Box 1 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 9)
  - Introduced February 23, 1954, H.J. Res. 390, Memorializing Christopher Columbus (Box 1 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 10)
  - Introduced May 13, 1954, H.R. 9133, To Amend the Classification Act of 1949, 1954-1956 (Box 1 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 11)
  - Introduced May 13, 1954, H.R. 9133, Classification Act, General Correspondence (Box 1 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 12)
  - Introduced January 5, 1955, H. Con. Res. 23, Prayer at the United Nations, 1955-1956 (Box 1 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 13)
  - Introduced January 5, 1955, H. Con. Res. 23, Prayer at the United Nations, General Correspondence, 1955-1956; Undated (Box 1 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 14-16)
  - Introduced January 5, 1955, H.R. 251, Taft Commemorative Stamp, 1954-1955 (Box 1 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 17)
  - Introduced January 5, 1955, H.R. 830, Certain Government Officers and Employees Excused from Duty to Vote in Elections, Undated (Box 1 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 18)
  - Introduced January 17, 1955, H. Con. Res. 30, Joint Committee on Intelligence Matters, 1955-1956 (Box 1 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 19)
  - Introduced January 26, 1955, H.R. 3085, To Amend the Classification Act of 1949, 1955-1956 (Box 1 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 20)
  - Introduced January 26, 1955, H.R. 3085, To Amend the Classification Act of 1949, General Correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 1 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 21-22)
  - Introduced February 24, 1955, H.R. 4401, Bill for Relief of Kalle K. Siermala, 1954-1956 (Box 1 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 23)
  - Introduced March 31, 1955, H.R. 5395, Compensation During Evading Capture by the Enemy, 1955-1956; Undated (Box 1 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 24)
  - Introduced March 31, 1955, H.R. 5395, Compensation During Evading Capture by the Enemy, General Correspondence, 1955-1957 (Box 1 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 25)
  - Introduced April 27, 1955, H.R. 5873, Autho. Prelim. Exam and Survey of the New England, N.Y., L.I. and N.J. Coastal and Tidal Areas (Box 1 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 26)
  - Introduced April 27, 1955, H.R. 5873, Autho. Prelim. Exam and Survey of the New England, N.Y., L.I. and N.J. Coastal and Tidal Areas, General Correspondence (Box 1 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 27)
  - Introduced January 3, 1956, H.J. Res. 438, Revision of Article VII of Status of Forces Agreement (1 of 2), 1953; 1955-1956; Undated (Box 1 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 28)
  - Introduced January 3, 1956, H.J. Res. 438, Revision of Article VII of Status of Forces Agreement (2 of 2), 1953; 1955-1956; Undated (Box 2 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 1)
  - Introduced January 3, 1956, H.J. Res. 438, Revision of Article VII of Status of Forces Agreement, General Correspondence, 1955 (Box 2 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 2)
  - Introduced January 3, 1956, H.J. Res. 438, Revision of Article VII of Status of Forces Agreement, General Correspondence (Box 2 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 3-4)
  - Introduced January 30, 1956, H.R. 8887, To Authorize Beach Erosion Control from Fire Island Inlet to Jones Inlet, 1941; 1948; 1952; 1954-1956; Undated (Box 2 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 5-6)
  - Introduced January 30, 1956, H.R. 8887, To Authorize Beach Erosion Control from Fire Island Inlet to Jones Inlet, General Correspondence (Box 2 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 7)
  - Introduced February 28, 1956, H.R. 9588, To Amend and Supplement Federal Aid Road Act, Undated (Box 2 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 8)
  - Introduced February 28, 1956, H.R. 9588, To Amend and Supplement Federal Aid Road Act, General Correspondence (Box 2 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 9)
  - Introduced June 6, 1956, H.R. 11642, For the Relief of Erma Murer (Box 2 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 10)
  - Introduced July 26, 1956, H. Con. Res. 272, Observance of the Ten Commandments, Undated (Box 2 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 11)
  - Introduced January 3, 1961, H.R. 64, To Amend the Railway Labor Act, 1960-1961; Undated (Box 2 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 12)
  - Introduced January 3, 1961, H.R. 64, To Amend the Railway Labor Act, General Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 2 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 13)
  - Introduced January 9, 1961, H.R. 2216, To Amend Title II of the Social Security Act, 1960-1962 (Box 2 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 14)
  - Introduced January 9, 1961, H.R. 2216, To Amend Title II of the Social Security Act, General Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 2 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 15)
  - Introduced January 16, 1961, H. Con. Res. 83, Qualification for Voting for Pres. and VP, Undated (Box 2 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 16)
  - Introduced January 16, 1961, H. Con. Res. 83, Qualification for Voting for Pres. and VP, General Correspondence (Box 2 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 17)
  - Introduced January 16, 1961, H. Con. Res. 84, Prayer at the UN, 1959 (Box 2 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 18)
  - Introduced January 16, 1961, H. Con. Res. 84, Prayer at the UN, General Correspondence, Undated (Box 2 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 19)
  - Introduced January 16, 1961, H.J. Res. 139, Resident Qualification for Voting for Pres. and VP, 1961-1962; Undated (Box 2 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 20)
  - Introduced January 16, 1961, H.J. Res. 140, Revision of the Status of Forces Agreement, 1955-1959; 1963 (Box 2 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 21)
  - Introduced January 16, 1961, H.J. Res. 140, Revision of the Status of Forces Agreement, General Correspondence, 1961-1963 (Box 2 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 22)
  - Introduced January 18, 1961, H. Con. Res. 113, Creates Select Committee of the H.O.R. on Fiscal Organization and Procedures of Congress (Box 2 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 23)
  - Introduced January 24, 1961, H.R. 3153, Career Compensation Act of 1949, Undated (Box 2 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 24)
  - Introduced January 24, 1961, H.R. 3153, Career Compensation Act of 1949, General Correspondence (Box 2 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 25)
  - Introduced January 31, 1961, H.R. 3639, To Amend the Internal Revenue Code of 1954, 1959-1961; Undated (Box 2 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 26)
  - Introduced January 31, 1961, H.R. 3639, To Amend the Internal Revenue Code of 1954, General Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 2 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 27)
  - Introduced February 7, 1961, H.R. 3942, To Prohibit Private Employment Agencies from Recruiting Minors for Out-of-State Employment, 1957-1959; Undated (Box 2 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 28)
  - Introduced February 7, 1961, H.R. 3942, To Prohibit Private Employment Agencies from Recruiting Minors for Out-of-State Employment, General Correspondence, 1957 (Box 2 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 29)
  - Introduced February 7, 1961, H.R. 3943, To Amend the War Claims Act of 1948, 1959 (Box 2 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 30)
  - Introduced February 27, 1961, H.R. 4887, To Provide for Issuance of Special Postal Stamp in Memory of Dr. Thomas A. Dooley (Box 2 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 31)
  - Introduced February 27, 1961, H.R. 4887, To Provide for Issuance of Special Postal Stamp in Memory of Dr. Thomas A. Dooley, General Correspondence (Box 2 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 32)
  - Introduced June 20, 1961, H.R. 7754, To Prescribe the Minimum Permissible Rate of Interest on Loans Made by the US, 1957 (Box 2 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 33)
  - Introduced June 20, 1961, H.R. 7754, To Prescribe the Minimum Permissible Rate of Interest on Loans Made by the US, General Correspondence (Box 2 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 34)
  - Introduced June 26, 1961, H. Con. Res. 359, Expressing the Sense of the H.O.R. with Respect to the US Policy Regarding Berlin (Box 2 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 35)
  - Introduced June 26, 1961, H. Con. Res. 359, Expressing the Sense of the H.O.R. with Respect to the US Policy Regarding Berlin, General Correspondence (Box 2 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 36)
  - Introduced June 26, 1961, H.R. 7873, For the Relief of Mrs. Maria Gonzalez Fernandez Long (Box 2 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 37)
  - Introduced August 8, 1961, H.R. 8554, To Amend the Federal Aviation Act of 1958 in Re: to Idlewild Airport, Undated (Box 2 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 38)
  - Introduced August 8, 1961, H.R. 8554, To Amend the Federal Aviation Act of 1958 in Re: to Idlewild Airport, General Correspondence (Box 2 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 39)
  - Introduced August 8, 1961, H.R. 8555, To Amend the Federal Aviation Act of 1958 in Re: to Flight Restrictions, 1961-1962; Undated (Box 2 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 40)
  - Introduced August 8, 1961, H.R. 8555, To Amend the Federal Aviation Act of 1958 in Re: to Flight Restrictions, General Correspondence (Box 2 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 41)
  - Introduced August 16, 1961, H. Con. Res. 373, No Reductions in Tariffs Made During Life of Reciprocal Trade Agreement Act (Box 2 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 42)
  - Introduced August 18, 1961, H.R. 8785, State Employee Retirement Systems on Behalf of the Civilian Employees of National Guard (Box 2 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 43)
  - Introduced August 18, 1961, H.R. 8785, State Employee Retirement Systems on Behalf of the Civilian Employees of National Guard, General Correspondence, Undated (Box 2 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 44)
  - Introduced August 30, 1961, H. Con. Res. 440, ASC to Make Study Re: Struggle with Soviet Imperialism (Box 2 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 45)
  - Introduced August 30, 1961, H. Con. Res. 440, ASC to Make Study Re: Struggle with Soviet Imperialism, General Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 2 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 46-48)
  - Becker Bills, General Correspondence, 1961 (Box 2 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 49)
  - Bills Which Mr. Becker May Introduce Next Year, 1961-1962 (Box 2 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 50)
  - Introduced February 20, 1962, H.R. 10277, To Amend Law Relating to Pay for Postal Employees (Box 2 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 51)
  - Introduced March 1, 1962, H. Res. 554, Establishing a Special Committee on Captive Natives (Box 2 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 52)
  - Introduced March 1, 1962, H. Res. 554, Establishing a Special Committee on Captive Natives, General Correspondence (Box 2 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 53)
  - Introduced May 1, 1962, H.R. 11520, Retention of Army and Air Nat. Guard Officers in Active Status Till 60 Years Old (Box 2 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 54)
  - Introduced May 10, 1962, H.R. 11690, To Provide for Research for Abating Objectionable Aircraft Noise, Undated (Box 3 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 1)
  - Introduced May 10, 1962, H.R. 11690, To Provide for Research for Abating Objectionable Aircraft Noise, General Correspondence (Box 3 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 2)
  - Introduced June 26, 1962, H.J. Res. 752, Amendment to Constitution for Offering Prayers in Public Schools and Places, 1962-1963; Undated (Box 3 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 3)
  - Introduced August 6, 1962, H.R. 12770, To Provide Under DC Laws to Life Imprisonment of Persons Convicted of 4 Felonies (Box 3 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 4)
  - Introduced August 6, 1962, H.R. 12770, To Provide Under DC Laws to Life Imprisonment of Persons Convicted of 4 Felonies, General Correspondence (Box 3 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 5)
  - Introduced August 6, 1962, H. Res. 744, Authorizing Committee on District of Columbia to Conduct Investigation and Study of Crimes in the District (Box 3 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 6)
  - Becker Bills, General, 1962 (Box 3 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 7)
  - Introduced January 9, 1963, H.R. 1356, Relief-Nicola Addano (Box 3 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 8)
  - Introduced January 9, 1963, H.R. 13404, For the Relief of Mark Blais Ellington, 1962-1964 (Box 3 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 9)
  - Introduced January 17, 1963, H.R. 1893, Life Imprisonment of Person Convicted of Four Felonies (Box 3 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 10)
  - Introduced January 17, 1963, H.R. 2074, To Amend SSA to Increase Outside Earnings Permitted Each Year, 1963-1964 (Box 3 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 11)
  - Introduced January 17, 1963, H. Res. 115, Stoppage of Back Door Spending Without Approval of Appropriations Committee (Box 3 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 12)
  - Introduced January 17, 1963, H. Res. 136, Investigation and Study of Crime in DC, 1962-1963 (Box 3 (3-Legislative Files), Folder 13)